GENIE, MAKE A WISH
- Someone's hacking the security system.
- What do they want?
Who is it? Russia? Or North Korea?
They're finding out now.
We should rush over.
SHOCK
SEDUCTION
Sleep well?
Let's kiss.
I need to plant onions.
Goodness me.
Done with the onions? Let's kiss.
Hold up. I left that thing back there.
Silly me.
You came back for this coffin?
- You've found it now, so let's kiss--
- Wait up. Stop.
This isn't something you can
just do whenever, you know?
You like rules, don't you?
These things have rules too.
- What are those rules?
- Well, those rules are…
First, the weather.
Rain. It must be raining.
Not yesterday.
It was the first time yesterday.
First kisses tend to be
more spontaneous,
less restricted by the rules.
But it must be raining for the second one.
And there must be alcohol.
Just after a drink. Right then.
It's that complex?
It's even more complex. I simplified it.
Now close this back up.
You're really mixing identities like this?
The first digit has changed again.
That fucking psycho bitch.
KI KA-YOUNG
BALANCE: 20,688,348,652 WON
And what's all this?
ESTIMATED ASSETS
4,300,431,074 WON
MONTHLY BILL
34,074,250 WON
CHEONGPUNGHO BANK
LUNCH BREAK
12 P.M. TO 1 P.M.
Ms. Gu, weren't you classmates
with Ki Ka-young and Choi Min-ji?
- Yes.
- Did you see their bags?
They're both Hermès.
She's just letting it sit on the floor.
Hey, could we get two iced Americanos?
He always does that
when we're headed to lunch.
You go ahead.
I'll take a soybean paste stew.
You really should open
a retirement savings fund account.
The earlier you plan for retirement,
the better.
I'm good. I don't need retirement.
What do you mean
you don't need retirement?
It's just Ms. Ki prefers
aggressive investments over low-risk ones.
Of course, I understand.
We should give you our new towel sets.
Ms. Gu? Where are they?
Did you forget?
Come on, Ms. Gu.
You should take more initiative.
I'll bring them right over.
Back to the topic of retirement, well…
How should I explain this?
The profitability…
As of today, construction is complete.
I just need a move-in date.
Do you like it?
Yes, Dad.
Daddy!
Goodness, you're blinding me!
My darling princess,
did you study hard today?
Like my life depended on it.
I'm tired as hell.
I was paired up
with the transfer student today.
- And?
- He's really cute.
He is? Did he become
the apple of your eye, Princess?
He seems really classy.
- So I asked where he lived.
- And?
- He lives in the mansion we talked about.
- Over there?
- Yeah.
- They moved in?
If they've moved in,
they should at least say hi.
Guess we'll have to make a house call.
Open up!
Wait, those rules
were this accurate?
Genie, tell me about tomorrow's weather.
Why would you ask me?
Weather is a touchy subject
for me right now!
Why are you making such a fuss
when I asked Genie?
Genie, so what's the weather
like tomorrow?
It's set to be a clear and sunny day
in Cheongpung tomorrow.
Hear that?
You should try asking it something.
It's so accurate.
Hey. Other Genie.
What does Ki Ka-young ask about the most?
Here is a list of Ms. Ki Ka-young's
recent search history.
Rainmaking ritual, artificial rain,
alcohol content of different beers,
cool-toned lip tint,
lightning-fast delivery,
rainmaking ritual…
What the hell have you done, you idiot?
Find out when it will rain this week.
I just checked since the cherry blossom
festival starts tomorrow.
Luckily, this entire week will be clear.
Damn it, why?
What about next week?
The spring rain hits next week,
so Monday may be the only dry day.
- Monday will be dry?
- Would you like it not to be?
You can do that?
- Since you're a mythical beast?
- I couldn't do it myself.
But I can try praying.
Not exactly useful.
What is this about?
Please put the wrench down.
Is something there?
I'm pretty today.
Pretty.
It's like the town is broke or something.
Why couldn't they get IU
for the festival--
What are you doing?
Put that down!
I'm pretty.
Even prettier than before.
Goodness, young lady.
There are mirrors all over this house!
It's not your fault, Master.
Psychopaths tend to be
pretty narcissistic.
Is that true?
Thank goodness.
I thought I must have
made her pretty somehow.
I was pretty awesome in the moment.
Why did I pick that moment
to get all competitive?
What are you talking about?
Now is the prime moment
to get competitive.
That kiss was the gateway to corruption.
Right. It should be, but…
After 1,000 years,
it was practically my first kiss.
I almost died from nerves.
I just feel bad for Ejllael.
I hear he hits the gym nonstop
because he wants to slit your throat.
Had he known a kiss would floor you,
he could've avoided all that effort.
By the way,
if it was your first in 1,000 years…
Yeah, what?
Shouldn't you have gotten
a dental scaling first?
Total jerk move.
Dental scaling?
What is that?
Raise your hand if you feel discomfort…
We haven't started yet.
Say, "Ah."
Bear with me for a moment.
You don't have any money?
And no ID?
You treated him with no intake info?
He said that he's a friend
of the auto shop owner, so…
Ka-young? But I'm her only friend…
Wait, are you the guy from the…
- Middle East?
- Min-ji? I'm so happy to see you!
I saw you eating gamja-tang together
at the gamja-tang place!
Does seeing us eat gamja-tang together
excuse you from paying?
A tab?
Ridiculous, isn't it?
It's outrageous, isn't it?
Apparently, he doesn't have ID.
And his name is none other than…
Lee Beul-li.
That immediately killed my curiosity,
so I stopped asking questions.
Do you even know anything
about this person?
One thing I know for certain
is that he isn't human.
No, of course he isn't.
No decent human racks up a tab
with someone they just met.
I'm feeling immense discomfort,
so here are my hands.
Seriously? I could just…
Dr. Choi, we need to get
to the festival to volunteer.
Okay. I'm coming.
At this rate,
you'll wind up in big trouble.
Snap out of it, Ms. Ki.
Okay, so he has a decent face,
and he's pretty tall.
And yeah, he has a velvety voice.
Other than that,
what's he got going for him?
It was essential given the rainy season.
I'll pay you back
once I become a pro gamer…
A pro gamer?
You've lost every game
to the neighborhood kid.
Pro gamer, you say?
Come here.
I dodged her pretty well today.
I was only hit on one side.
What the heck?
Ms. Ki.
Check the tire pressure for me, would you?
Sure.
You're drinking.
Yes, that I am.
And you're at the wheel
with the engine on.
Yes, I'm at the wheel.
Engine?
What's that?
All right, sir.
Blow into this for us.
And what's this? Is it a pipe?
Go on.
- Okay, more.
- More.
- Harder.
- Harder!
Hello, Homies!
It's Da-jin of Sky Farm Life.
I'm coming to you today from
the Cheongpungho Cherry Blossom Festival.
Let's start off by raiding
the For Daughter Strawberry stand.
Guys, what do you call a strawberry
that was fired from its job?
What?
Berry upset!
Right. "Berry upset!"
You're hilarious!
See that? Nothing flops for no reason.
That was great.
- Cherry blossoms!
- Indeed.
Open wide. That's it.
Can we try opening up a little wider?
Even wider!
Hello. We're from Cheongpungho Bank.
We have a savings event,
so visit for a consultation.
Hello.
Where is the bathroom?
Is the subway station close by?
Without cilantro, please.
What are you saying?
Are you an Arab?
You spoke Korean just fine earlier.
He doesn't want any cilantro.
What?
Arabic was big back in school,
so I took it as my second language.
I'll try speaking to him.
My name is Oh Gyeong-yeol,
a police officer
from the Republic of Korea.
Sir, you have violated the traffic laws--
Get over here.
You said speaking Arabic would work.
About that. It worked for me
toward the end of the Joseon dynasty…
Just go. I'll handle things here.
I could just…
Oh Pan-geum!
Buy that to eat. That one.
Why are you walking around
eating raw tofu?
I hear this is post-police food.
Oh Pan-geum, you should drink
some black goat extract.
To live a long life.
I don't have that kind of money!
Why don't you buy me one, then?
I can't buy things for you.
I only make recommendations.
Honestly, I can't tell
if you're a bastard or just pitiful.
Goodness me.
- What?
- Hey, would you look at that?
Goodness, that puppy
is bouncing around on its own.
How incredible, no?
- Wow. What is this?
- Come and have a look.
- How adorable!
- It's walking!
It's so cool.
Hey, it's walking
but still stays in the same spot.
How is that?
At least her joints seem strong.
My apologies.
What is it?
There's this thing called fireworks today.
Do you know when and where?
The fireworks?
They'll be set off after the sun sets.
You'd get the best view from there.
Enjoy.
The best view is that way?
Ta-da.
Damn, that fucker
looked like he was loaded.
But he was broke, damn it.
Well, well. Look at these motherfuckers
with no common decency.
What do you think
you're doing on our turf?
We thought we'd visit
the cherry blossom festival.
The spring breeze is a-blowing.
The cherry blossom festival is our turf.
We didn't go against the current to invade
your cherry salmon festival, did we?
You could always come to next year's.
What, should we send you an invite?
Great, you should all get prosthetics
while you're here.
You know the health services
in Cheongpung are first-class.
- What the…
- What the heck?
What a relief! I almost got beat up
by the lump of clay again.
And who's this prick?
Hey, which gang are you from?
- What?
- Why isn't he answering me?
Just fucking wipe them all out!
Darn it. I'm in the mood for flowers.
- Damn you!
- Hey, you bastard!
Wow.
Goodness me.
Oh boy.
How stunning.
AS SEXY
FUCK YOU
What the…
Goodness me, is that…
Is that my Ka-young's name up there?
"As, sexy, fuck, you"?
Wait, what does that mean?
So that prick does have money.
KI KA-YOUNG
YOU'RE IN MY HEART
So women really love those words?
Yes, I told you.
Just trust me with these things.
They go absolutely wild.
She'll be corrupted in no time.
Perfect.
KI KA-YOUNG
FUCK YOU
That son of a gun.
That's what I always think
when I see Iblis too.
I'm glad you relate, Ms. Ki Ka-young.
What brings you here? You don't even
have a car since you can fly.
Everyone in the village
is at the festival.
I came as things are quiet.
Do you have something to say to me?
I won't return your feather.
It's yours.
What species are you, anyway?
Just as there are Yorkshire terriers
and Chihuahuas,
there are humans, angels, devils,
and genies. So which are you?
I'm obviously his servant.
You saw my wings. I'm an angel.
Right, an angel?
I thought I'd double-check
since your wings were black.
You do volunteer lunch runs, right?
For a while, I've been thinking it's odd
how every time you deliver lunch,
the elderly person
ends up dead.
I guess one could see it that way,
but try switching the order of events.
I visit dying elders to bring them peace.
I see.
One more thing.
Several of your buildings are within
a one-kilometer radius of my auto shop,
and you never hid your identity from me.
Are you spying on me?
I am. To be more precise,
I'm working on his orders.
What are they? His orders?
"If there comes a moment that Iblis
bows his head before a human, you shall
slit your brother's throat."
Isn't that thrilling?
That's why I'm going to do my best
to make sure Iblis doesn't win you over.
It's too late.
Pardon?
Get lost so I can close shop.
Right.
Is that the time?
But why are you being so rude?
Who knows? Maybe because psychopaths
can't hide their displeasure?
Or because you're trying to kill him
when I'm his master?
Or maybe because
he's already won me over.
Which of these do you think it is?
I knew I was right about her.
A STUDY OF PSYCHOPATHS
Did something happen?
- I brought the books--
- Throw them out again.
Psychopath? I'm absolutely certain!
I should've known it was too lucky.
At this rate, there's no telling
about her last two wishes.
Should I have taken my scythe with me?
She had the audacity
to tell me to "get lost."
Like she was dismissing me!
- To you, Master?
- Yes.
You do look a little young for your age.
Did you see the fireworks?
Weren't they cool?
I did that, you know.
Why did you choose that…
Please, no!
Hey, no using cheats like that!
So you were behind the fireworks?
Yes.
I wondered
which crazy fool was behind them.
Crazy what?
Hey, where do you live?
Lead the way, punk.
And where do you live?
Lead the way.
Pardon?
The typical psychopath
will harm others
to get what they want.
But my dear Ka-young
is a little different.
Her grandma and the entire neighborhood
rallied to raise her with hope,
so even though she may not feel guilt,
she knows to stay
within her learned boundaries.
All right. So what?
So I'm saying I don't like you, you jerk.
Ka-young will stay within those boundaries
no matter what,
and I will protect Ka-young
as she does so.
Whether it be psychologically…
or physically.
I'm her knight in shining armor, you see.
You are, aren't you?
All this time,
I thought you were a girl! Wow!
This is on the house.
Why are you laughing?
Funniest thing I've heard in 983 years.
Nine hundred and eighty…
What the hell are you talking about?
Now that we have a man in the mix,
you come to a seafood stew joint?
I can't believe you.
I didn't come. I just stopped by.
I'll drop Min-ji off,
so I'll see you at home.
Can't I take her home?
We've actually bonded. Honestly. Master?
Just call me "ma'am."
Do you need anything else?
Benevolence?
Min-ji didn't pay before she left,
but I'm…
I'm completely broke.
I know about that. Allow me.
I've reached 112, right?
I'm turning myself in.
Eating without paying? Seriously?
This is unfair. I didn't even eat.
I just did the "not paying" part.
Shut it.
Why did you call me to bail you out?
What about the one who's like you?
That angel!
You're mistaken about that.
Not only are Ejllael and I
different species, we're on bad terms.
You and I are also on bad terms.
What's with you lowering your voice?
I may be Satan,
but this is no laughing matter.
Ejllael and I fought a long battle.
The war was devastating for me too.
Why did you go to war?
He created angels from light
and genies from smokeless fire.
The genies created from fire
grew increasingly arrogant,
even aspiring to surpass Him.
In his rage, he sent the angels
and ordered them to decimate us.
The angels came down
and began slaughtering all the genies,
and Ejllael led the charge.
The war lasted 300 years,
and I lost most of my brothers
as a result.
So your quarrels turn into
full-blown wars of the gods?
I've rarely seen my brothers since then.
Partly because I defied his orders
and ended up in hell.
And once released, I ended up trapped
for almost 1,000 years, so there's that.
Where are your surviving brothers now?
I'm not sure.
They're probably inhabiting rings or lamps
or living out their days in a pot.
They may be controlling sleep…
or tending to the flowers of souls.
Or perhaps controlling the rain.
One controls the rain?
- What?
- Can't you find him? Find him and--
Can't. No longer with us.
I think Sade is looking for me.
I'm pretty sure
Sade isn't looking for you.
Wow.
Miss, does the owner of this car
live in this neighborhood?
Yes.
Must be a crypto bro.
I used to drive one of these.
That's the 2024 model.
Hey, come on!
I said to patch the puncture,
not take the tire off!
It needs to be changed.
Did you even report all these?
Every one of these modifications?
What are you, a civil servant?
Why would I report anything?
Hey, put it back on.
Where do you live?
Why do you ask?
Like what you see?
Just concerned
you'll croak on your way home.
Did you do these wheels yourself?
You shoved them on
when they don't even fit.
A simple patch-up wouldn't last an hour.
I've explained everything,
so call a tow truck and take it away.
I won't fix it.
Is this how you treat your customers?
Hey, get over here.
Is everything good?
You drank that?
There were so many bottles.
Weren't they for staff?
No wonder they kept going missing.
Wait, what were you saying?
I was just asking
for the tow truck number.
Zero, one, zero,
six, three, four…
- Wait, I didn't catch that.
- Two…
Did you hit him?
Six, three, four…
What are you going to do
about this random, dreamy vibe?
I'm sorry. I'll report everything.
- I swear.
- Where are you going?
- Damn it.
- Don't go.
Hello, ma'am.
- Hello.
- Thank you. Feel free to browse.
Who's in charge of this display?
Who's responsible for this station?
Hey, you're back!
I'm sorry, Im-seon.
I had to step out for a moment.
My bowels were acting up again.
Don't you think it's wrong
to call your branch manager by name?
At our age, we're all a little unwell.
Is it too much to ask you to do your job?
I can't take any more of this crap.
Ms. Jung Yeong-sun. What did you just say?
I said I can't stand it anymore.
This is so ridiculous that I quit.
Im-seon, this is just wrong.
Has the late promotion gone to your head?
Ms. Jung Yeong-sun!
I don't know how you were even promoted,
but is this how you treat your coworkers?
We've all heard the rumors
about you taking bribes from vendors.
Do we look like fools?
Yeong-sun, please!
How could I be so stupid?
I shouldn't have asked to be
a branch manager at this age.
People look down on me,
and I keep making mistakes.
I guess I could get to it a bit quicker.
Excuse me?
Here's my second wish.
Take me back 20 years
and make me branch manager then.
If I'd made branch manager back then,
just imagine all the money.
Shall we go, then?
Twenty years into the past?
BRANCH MANAGER
KANG IM-SEON
Go through that door,
and it will be 20 years in the past,
and you will still be the branch manager.
Talk to me.
Why are you alone?
Where's Dad? He said he'd pick you up.
Dad has work to do.
Long time no see.
Do you still like hot chamomile tea?
Yes. I'm still a psychopath,
so caffeine isn't good for me.
You haven't changed a bit.
I thought you'd at least ask,
"What brings you here?"
I moved here with my wife and son.
Take good care of us. I found out
about this place thanks to you.
I don't recall ever telling you
exactly where I live.
Not many University of Science grads
run auto shops.
I guess.
Either way, it's good to see you again.
You look great.
How's business?
True joy.
I guess the house looked
pretty much the same 20 years ago.
Except for you.
You grow up to be super pretty
20 years from now.
So careful with this.
You wouldn't want to hurt…
What is it?
Someone just entered my memory.
Grandma told me not to speak to strangers.
Leave!
Wait, no!
Hey, you startled me.
So you're clearly as odd as ever.
"So you're clearly as odd as ever."
He was sleazy as hell.
So how did you hurt your head again?
Who else would it be?
She was even worse 20 years ago.
Did you visit the past for a wish?
Yeah.
That'll be 18,000 won.
I need to see your ID for the alcohol…
Ms. Ki!
What's wrong? Is something up?
Just that it's raining.
Keep up the good work.
Where the hell is he?
Wait, what?
Why is it stopping?
But it's the rainy season!
Where the hell were you? It rained!
Do you know how long
I looked everywhere for you?
Seriously?
Hey, you're the one
who took a rock this big, you know.
You do all that,
then I hear about you acting all "odd."
You're deflecting because you're cornered.
I'm in a corner? Who was the jerk
who came by the auto shop?
I heard you were giggling with each other.
Kiss me or crack my skull,
but just do one.
You can't do both, you serial kisser!
I can't?
Then I choose to crack your skull.
Come here.
Hey, come on. You're my master.
Shush. We're talking right now.
Come on. Treat me with care.
Take care of me.
I said shush!
Why does every damn dog around here
bark like mad whenever they see you?
They're just scared I'll take them in.
They need to read human expressions,
but I don't have any.
Hey, I don't plan on taking you in either!
Sade!
I am Genie, the lamp spirit.
…shall grant you three wishes…
…no traveling to the future.
Anything besides that,
your wish… is my command.
But before that,
tell all the dogs in the area
to stop barking at Ki Ka-young.
If they bark one more time,
I'll change every last one of you
into cats.
Tell him.
Ki Ka-young.
MUTT, AGE 7
MADE FIRST WISH ON MAY 16, 2024
TO BECOME A PERSON, WITH SPECIFICS
CHARMING MIDDLE-AGED MAN IN HIS 40S
WHO RESEMBLES DANIEL HENNEY
Now that's not a face
you see in these parts.
Is there a film shoot?
Remember I was depressed
about losing my eyesight with age?
- Yeah?
- I think I just fully recovered.
- Let's go, Yeong-sun.
- Sure.
Wow.
I'm hungry.
Chicken and beer?
Sounds good. Let's do it.
Suit and slicked back hair.
Wow, he's doggone handsome.
He's coming this way.
Hand me some blotting paper and lip tint.
- What's he doing?
- He must be crazy!
My gosh!
They say handsome men
are either gay or dogs.
His actions clearly show
he's a total mutt.
You've run out of water.
Don't skip breakfast tomorrow.
Pardon?
The food doesn't taste good.
It's too bland.
It's too bland for you?
I should have been
more generous with the salt.
I was only joking.
What will happen to me now?
A question I'm tired of getting.
One thing's for certain.
I'll be saving on the cost of salt.
Yes, Grandma?
Ka-young, you're not seeing
things again, are you?
You're taking your meds, right?
Every dose without missing any?
Yes, you see me take them every day. Why?
If you have any wishes, just tell me.
I'll make them all come true.
Wishes?
What is this in the notebook in your room?
Did you like Daniel Henney?
You can see that?
She can see that?
Wait, was it always visible
to everyone else's eyes?
You're seriously asking me that?
This damn magic has way too many holes.
This won't do.
We need a safe space
to hide the notebook and pen.
Your lamp.
Are you sure
only you and Sade can get in?
If they really wanted to,
Ejllael or Irem probably could.
But even you couldn't.
So it must be safe.
What does it look like inside the lamp?
Is it cozy?
It's dismal.
Do you see this?
Do you get a sense of how lonely
I must have been for 983 years?
Sorry, but I don't know
what loneliness is.
But you do know to be sorry?
Of course I don't.
But Min-ji told me that leading with that
makes me seem considerate.
And you know what considerate is?
Yes. That one's quite easy.
I just need to be honest.
For instance, it's something like this.
I heard it all from that brother of yours.
That you'll get your throat slit
if you bow your head to a righteous human.
Ejllael, that prick!
That was considerate? Not a threat?
Are you seriously not
scared of me?
To be honest, I don't know what fear is.
But Grandma did say
that apathy is the scariest.
My grandma is an incredibly fragile
safety feature to my apathy.
If that safety feature…
were to disappear,
there's a chance
my violence would take over,
so I'm making preparations.
But you'd know all that from spying on me.
"As natural a death as possible."
I do know, yes.
Like deep-sea equipment failure
or a fall on a remote trail.
But why do all that when you don't have
emotions or any affection for humans?
I am a stone in a shoe
to the people of the world.
I make people uncomfortable.
So I'm removing that stone for them.
For my grandma.
So if you're going to kill me, hurry.
And don't go getting your throat slit.
Ejllael?
The more I see that angel,
the less I like him.
- Whatever you do, don't lose to him.
- Wait, you're actually taking my side?
- Shouldn't I?
- You shouldn't. If you do, then…
You know?
I'm going to wring
your neck.
That would make things strange.
We're already strange.
You and I are both antisocial,
so why am I under scrutiny
while you're admired?
What exactly was his purpose
in making you and me meet?
That's it.
I should have been pondering that.
Not totally clueless.
Okay, we need furniture.
Bring over the table and chairs
I made in the workshop.
No matter which way I look at it,
I don't think you made these.
They seem to be made
by a giant corporation.
Don't talk back!
You now have two pieces of furniture.
It'd be nice to have another rug,
wouldn't it?
This way. Here.
Starting the cleaning cycle.
Why the hell is this…
Is this used to fix things
or to destroy them?
That all depends on you.
Hey!
Go that way, and you won't come back.
It'd take over 1,000 years.
That thing.
It's coming together.
Now I feel somewhat reassured.
About Ms. Im-seon.
She could have done whatever she wanted
beyond the supermarket,
so I wonder why
she didn't just leave the supermarket.
That's how humans are.
They dream of being king
but fear leaving their domain.
They've seen how kings rule by force,
and so they wish for the same.
That's the cowardly nature of humans
and the reason why I hate them.
He may not be clueless,
but he's also not big on enlightenment.
Humans hate you too.
So that's another use for that.
If I killed you on behalf of all humans,
would I go to heaven?
You think it would end at that?
He'd give you heaven if you asked.
Come here. Get over here.
Come here.
Get over here.
- I said come.
- I don't want to.
I LAUGH IN MY DREAMS, JOYFULLY
- Let's keep it humane and…
- But you're not human.
Where is that mumbling coming from?
I can hear sound coming from this.
Is it a radio?
Pan-geum!
Pan-geum, are you home?
Yes, I'm here!
Goodness, you came all this way
in the pouring rain?
I think she said…
it's raining.
It seems that way, doesn't it?
Do you have any alcohol here?
Should I buy some?
Wouldn't it be faster…
to go together?
Don't forget we need money to buy alcohol.
- This is all I need.
- You'll use that as collateral?
- My goodness. What shall we do?
- Grandma?
Grandma, why are you crying?
- Good heavens.
- What is it?
Why is she crying?
We just heard
that the craftsman, Mr. Kim, died.
You know, the man
who taught you how to carve wood.
Then why is my grandma crying?
She's crying because she's sad.
She's sad that her friend died.
This is exactly why, you know.
Why people call you a psycho.
Heung-rye!
What?
Goodness me!
Death makes life seem so futile.
It brings me to tears.
My goodness.
It's so tragic. I can't bear it.
How can you
cast the world aside like this?
Even so, they say he passed peacefully
as if drifting off to sleep.
Consider that a good death.
There's no such thing as a good death.
I guess you kids would have no idea,
with your entire lives ahead of you.
I'm not afraid of dying,
but if I think of my darling Ka-young…
What if my heart suddenly stops
or I have a stroke and collapse?
What if I get cancer and diabetes
and end up with dementia too?
Good heavens,
how would she ever take care of me?
Why would you think such silly thoughts?
At that moment, I realized that Grandma
must have read the same articles as me.
"An aging society is coming fast."
"Prepare yourself
for age-related illness."
"Medical Tomorrow."
I was going to die if Grandma died,
but Grandma actually wants
to live a long and healthy life.
So your point is?
I'll make my second wish.
Make my grandma young.
The same age as me.
This is my second wish.
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi